I made it!
Deer Meets Darkness Girl
Introducing once more,
Koshi Torako, former delinquent.
Covering up her past upon joining high school,
she climbed the ranks as an honor student
and is now president of
the student council, as well as class rep.
However a transfer deer (?) named
Shikanoko Noko revealed her past,
revealed that she was a virgin,
and because she was a total pushover,
she was duped into becoming
the president of the mysterious Deer Club.
And once again, she reluctantly
heads to the club.
Yay! It's time for Deer Club!
Maybe she doesn't sound reluctant?
Well, it's not like I'm actually
looking forward to going to the club.
Oh? Then what is it?
When I gave the clubhouse
a little makeover this morning,
it turned out so good!
But it's not like I'm super excited
for club activities today
or anything like that.
Is that so?
It's the president's job to make
the clubhouse a comfortable place.
I can't wait to see how she reacts!
You're amazing, Koshitan!
I was wrong about you!
Of course!
All that's left is the wallpaper...
Oh! And maybe I'll get a cabinet!
There's still so much to be done!
Just you wait! It'll be my own utopia!
I won't forgive you, Deer
And thus, the utopia came to an end.
Kumagoro!
Wh-What is this? My utopia!
The utopia I spent my life savings on
and four hours of my morning!
She woke up at 3 AM.
Are you okay, Koshitan?
It's dangerous there. Come over here.
You! Did you do this?!
Did you do this to my utopia?!
Hm? What are you talking about?
It was already like this when I got here.
Also, this room is dangerous.
What do you mean?
Someone's trying to kill me today.
Who? And why?
I don't know.
But it's probably the same person
who trashed our room.
I fell into a five-meter-deep pitfall
on the way to school,
spears came falling out of the sky,
and there were plastic bottles
filled with water everywhere.
How are you still alive?!
Didn't a spear stab you in the head?!
And water bottles? Not even cats are
scared of those anymore!
And my antlers totally
got stuck in the door, too!
You broke it again?!
Anyway! I'm telling you,
this place is dangerous!
Now, calm down.
Just think about it.
There's no way someone's after you.
You think so?
Of course.
Let's just step outside,
get some fresh air and think calmly—
Hey, how could you step
out of cover so carelessly?
This is a battlefield!
Who are you?!
I thought I taught you that
carelessness will get you killed!
You never taught me a damn thing!
I was born in the Heisei era of peace!
But more importantly,
is someone seriously after you?
Looks like it.
Man, screw this! I'm leaving!
What?! You're going to abandon
your teacher and run away?!
Shut up! Since when am I your student?
I'm done getting caught up
in all this annoying—
Koshitan, is your head all right?
That's not an insult.
Who the hell are you?
Give me back my utopia!
Now she's pissed.
You're going down!
I don't care if you're
a soldier or an assassin.
Bring it on!
Crap! Grenade! Get down!
Deer crackers?!
Hey! It's a trap!
Wait, you moron! Wait, wait, wait!
What, Koshitan?!
Open your eyes! It's a trap!
It's the trap of all traps!
What kind of idiot drools
and walks right into a trap?!
- A trap...
- Shikanoko?
Long, long ago, a deer was asked,
"Why do deer eat deer crackers?"
This is how they answered.
"Because there are
deer crackers before me!"
Shikanoko!
I'm sorry, Koshitan.
But I love deer crackers
more than anything in this world!
Yippee!
Well, I messed up.
I told you that this was a trap—
I lost a little speed at the end
and couldn't reach the deer crackers!
You're still on that?!
Hey! You over there trying to get me!
I know you can hear me!
My name is Nokotan! Show yourself!
I accept this fight fair and square!
Haven't you lost already?
The deer's distant cry of defeat.
And bring me more deer crackers, please!
You're asking them for favors?
You're quite bold for a pest.
I planned to exterminate you earlier
but my calculations were all wrong.
A fight? I'll happily accept.
I'll send you on your way to hell.
This girl...
I've managed to survive countless battles
but she was able to capture me with ease.
She's on another level.
Who the hell are you?!
- Anko?
What the hell are you doing here?
Onee-chan!
I missed you so much!
You missed me?
You see me at home every day.
I want to be with you 365 days a year,
24 hours a day, every minute and second!
I can't get enough of your scent!
Cut it out, will you?
And why aren't you at school?
Even your angry face is so adorable!
I wuv you so much!
Are you even listening?
Who's she, Koshitan?
My bad, this is Koshi Anko.
My little sister.
Koshi... Anko... Red bean... paste!
You're imagining something
delicious, aren't you?
Don't stare at me like that, you vermin!
Shikanoko Noko. I cannot forgive you.
What's your deal with her?
Wait, did you do all this?
Yes. It was me.
Why would you...
It's all this deer's fault! All of it!
It's her fault you changed!
You used to come running home
to me after school.
To you? That's where we live as a family.
You've been coming home so late...
I'm always home by seven!
I followed you because I was curious
about why you were out so late
and you were alone with
that deer in your "club."
How obscene!
What's obscene is your damn way of thinking!
And you left early again this morning...
All you think about
is your little deer love nest!
That comfy couch, those cute rugs?!
Is all of that necessary for a club room?
Obscene! What were you two
planning on doing in there?!
W-Well...
She wanted to retort, but couldn't admit
that the setup was for herself.
You can't answer? Does that mean...
You slept together?
Of course not!
Are you mentally ill?
And what's with the kunai?!
Are you Iga? Koga? A Hokage?
Hey, help me out here.
Koshitan is my girl!
That's not helping!
Why are you complicating things?
That's not what's going on here!
I don't know if you're chunky or smooth,
but I will protect Koshitan!
You've done it now, you idiot!
I knew it! You took my
sister's virginity, didn't you?!
See?! I knew this would happen!
Do you know how hard I've been
protecting my sister's virginity?!
I don't remember asking for that.
I won't forgive you...
The deer that took my sister from me
and my sister who crossed
that line with a deer.
I haven't crossed any lines!
Not even the Chuo Line!
Setting: Hino City
I belong by your side.
Anyone who stands in my way is my enemy.
That's why I decided to destroy it all.
Anko...
I thought that if I destroyed
this ridiculous Deer Club of yours
and exterminated that vermin,
my sister would come back home to me.
But I've changed my mind.
You mentioned something
about fighting fair and square, right?
That sounds fun. I accept.
But if I win,
you'll spend the rest of your life
as a deer at Nara Park.
Nara?
If I lose, I will accept the festering
relationship you have with my sister
and leave you alone.
You're gonna give people the wrong idea!
Pull yourself together, Anko.
This is ridiculous.
There's no point in fighting.
Why? It was the deer's idea.
That is true...
Fine. Let's fight.
Wait, are you serious?
If you become a Nara Park deer,
what will happen to the club?
Don't worry, Koshitan.
Trust me!
The Deer Club has a bond
harder than deer crackers!
Shikanoko...
What are you even talking about?!
Deer crackers aren't hard! They're flaky!
I have one condition, too.
What?
If I win the fight...
Give me tons of deer crackers.
Just go to Nara already!
The Deer Club faces its first huge crisis!
What will happen to the club? To Nokotan?
The battle that will decide the fate of
Deer Club and deer crackers begins now!
I'm deporting you to Nara Park immediately!
All the deer crackers I can eat...
Can I go home now?
MIYAJIMA
O-TORII
ITSUKUSHIMA SHRINE
1st Hinominami High School
Chitty Chitty King of Koshi Torako Competition!!
The first-ever Hinominami High School Chitty
Chitty King of Koshi Torako Competition!
Let's introduce our competitors!
What the hell is this?!
Koshi Torako's little sister
with a fierce sister complex,
Koshi Anko-chan!
Does anything in this world even
matter other than me and my sister?
No, really! What is this?!
The Deer Club's resident deer,
Shikanoko Noko-san!
I'll do it for the deer crackers!
Are any of you listening to me?!
How do you feel about
the competitors, Koshi-san?
I... I'm so lost right now.
You sure sound excited!
Are my words reaching you at all?!
And today's grand prizes are...
For Anko-chan, the right to deport
Nokotan to Nara Park!
And for Nokotan,
a 100-year supply of deer crackers!
Where did you even get all of these?
And your host will be me, Ukai,
the advisor of the Deer Club!
Do teachers have nothing else to do?
All right! Let's get started!
You spent way too much money on this set.
Question one.
What does Koshi-san do every—
What does Koshi-san do
every night before bed?
She talks the plushies in her room
and gives them all a goodnight kiss.
Correct!
Stop! What kind of question is that?!
Why are you violating my privacy?!
Is that a bad thing?
Of course it is!
But it's making your fans
love you even more!
- She likes plushies?
- Adorable!
Fan for life!
That's not the issue here!
Here's a photo to prove it!
Privacy! My privacy!
Stop it with these questions!
- On to the second question!
- You're ignoring me?!
Is Koshi-san currently—
Tch!
Nokotan was quicker this time!
Your answer, please!
Is Koshitan currently without a bra?
The answer is she's wearing
a bra top, therefore, without a bra.
Again, what are these questions?!
Correct!
Y-You can't prove that without looking!
Schrödinger's bra.
Let's take a look at the footage!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Seriously! Why do you have this footage?!
Question three!
Can I go home now?!
Koshi-san has da—
Koshi-san has dated
how many boys or girls in total?
The answer is zero!
Uh, I might have dated someone!
She hasn't.
Sorry, incorrect!
Koshi-san has dated
zero boys or girls in total,
but what is the reason for this?
Please answer in sixty characters or less.
Do you really need to dig that deep?!
The answer please, Anko-chan!
Anko
Others dated as she waited for
her first love due to shojo manga brain rot.
Exactly sixty characters.
Correct!
Stop analyzing me!
Her favorite manga magazine
is Bessatsu Friend.
Question four!
What is Koshi-san's childhood secret?
She wet the bed until she was ten.
Correct!
Don't say that!
What is something that Koshi-san
surprisingly likes?
- She likes kids' anime.
- Correct!
Why is that surprising? Who cares?
Question five! What is Koshi-san's—
- Egg on rice!
- Correct!
How were you able to answer that?!
What's happened here?
The contestants are locked in a tie!
How much longer are they going to
violate my privacy?
Something isn't right!
Why does this freaky deer
know so much about my sister?
There must be something going on!
I know! She's connected to the all-deer
network, Shika Shika Network (SSN)!
It's collecting my sister's data,
sending it to the supercomputer Shikagaku
to be analyzed and
transmitted to her antlers!
Now, I'll have to show you my true power!
You've let your guard down.
I have plenty more traps left!
Doesn't this make
the quiz completely pointless?
Koshitan's privacy
was violated for nothing.
I'll make Shish Kebab out of you
before I send you to Nara Park!
You can dodge them?!
What is up with this deer?
Take my knives like an adult!
Take this! And this!
I'm tired. No one's looking.
Maybe I'll just leave.
You vermin!
Onee-chan!
Shikanoko!
Hey, Shikanoko!
Koshitan... I'm getting really sleepy...
What are you saying?!
Stay with me, Shikanoko!
Open your eyes, Shikanoko! Shikanoko!
Why?
Following me around,
making me join your club...
Getting us into this mess...
How dare you...
How dare you just leave me like this?!
Notsu!
Shikanoko, you're alive!
I'm glad you're alive, but how?
Earlier...
It looks like the crackers protected me.
What is this, an old movie?
Deer crackers aren't even hard,
they're flaky!
Shikanoko.
Thank you for saving my sister.
This was my loss.
I was so foolishly blinded
by hate and anger,
I almost hurt my own sister.
I've failed as a little sister!
You're the one who should be by her si—
That's not true.
It's not true.
It was you, no...
Koshian, I was able to save your sister
thanks to the deer crackers you gave me.
You saved her life!
I think we can be good friends!
Can I call you Nokotan?
Of course!
Take care of my sister, okay, Nokotan?
Leave it to me, Koshian.
Nokotan! Koshian!
How lovely!
In the end, Koshitan still had no idea
what was going on.
Starting tomorrow,
I'm going to wear a bra every day.
The next day
It's white today!
X-ray vision?!